<mos>
<mosID>MOS281.MOS</mosID>
<ncsID>MOS281.NCS</ncsID>
<roStorySend>
<roID>DEMOENPS50VPC;P_OSM\W;AADC7235-007A-4317-BE112095DF74356A</roID>
<storyID>DEMOENPS50VPC;P_OSM\W\R_AADC7235-007A-4317-BE112095DF74356A;7ABF108E-CF47-4CAB-8759DA3F4E6A48F0</storyID>
<storySlug>MOS Server Countdowns</storySlug>
<storyNum></storyNum>
<storyBody><p>MOS Server 2:48 countdowns:</p>
<p> </p><storyItem><itemID>2</itemID><itemSlug>Rename story slug-2</itemSlug><objID>M000123</objID><mosID>MOS.Server.rdm1.bnc.ap.mos</mosID><mosAbstract><b>Hotel Fire</b><em>vo</em>          :30</mosAbstract><objPaths><objPath techDescription="MPEG2 Video">\\server\media\clip392028cd2320s0d.mxf</objPath><objProxyPath techDescription="WM9 750Kbps">http://server/proxy/clipe.wmv</objProxyPath></objPaths><objDur>1800</objDur><objTB>60</objTB><mosExternalMetadata><mosScope>STORY</mosScope><mosSchema>http://MOSA4.com/mos/supported_schemas/MOSAXML2.08</mosSchema><mosPayload><Owner>SHOLMES</Owner><ModTime>20010308142001</ModTime><mediaTime>0</mediaTime><TextTime>278</TextTime><ModBy>LJOHNSTON</ModBy><Approved>0</Approved><Creator>SHOLMES</Creator><objType>VIDEO</objType></mosPayload></mosExternalMetadata></storyItem>
<p>BEIJING, China (CNN) -- A strong aftershock hit parts of China already devastated by an earthquake Friday, triggering landslides, blocking roads, knocking out phone lines and burying vehicles, state-run media reported.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Rescue workers recover bodies from a collapsed building in Dujiangyan Friday as relatives look on.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>1 of 4more photos »  The 5.5-magnitude earthquake rattled Sichuan province shortly after President Hu Jintao arrived in the quake zone on Friday to get a first-hand look at the devastated region.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>It was just the latest of dozens of tremors that continue to fray nerves across the region.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>As frantic search-and-rescue efforts entered a fifth day, the official death toll issued by authorities in Sichuan Province now stood at 22,069, with 14,000 still buried, 159,000 injured and 4.8 million homeless, according to China&#39;s Xinhua state news agency. China&#39;s state council said Thursday that the number of dead could eventually top 50,000.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Yet hope still emerged from amid the horror of the nation&#39;s worst disaster in recent years, with survivors pulled from the rubble four days after being buried by the 7.9 magnitude earthquake that rocked southwestern China Monday afternoon.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Rescuers pulled a student from the debris of Beichuan Middle School, 80 hours after the quake collapsed the building, Xinhua reported.  Watch student being pulled from the rubble after 80 hours. »</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Two more people were saved after being buried for 95 hours, the agency added. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Rescuers said they could hear a weak yell for help from under the building&#39;s rubble and are &quot;expecting more miracles,&quot; according to state-run media.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Don&#39;t Miss</p>
<p>China&#39;s new disaster openness </p>
<p>iReport:  Total chaos, small miracles </p>
<p>Faces of dead wear mask of pain </p>
<p>Losses compounded by one-child policy </p>
<p>Hu flew to Mianyang in the hard-hit Sichuan province, which has become a massive refugee camp for survivors, China&#39;s Xinhua news agency reported.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>&quot;The challenge is still daunting, the task is still arduous and the time pressing,&quot; Hu said.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Thousands of people who were uprooted around the region have taken shelter at the city&#39;s main sports gym and other facilities. Reports say 7,395 people have died and 18,645 are trapped in debris in the city.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Xinhua reported 135,000 Chinese troops and medics are involved in the rescue effort across 58 counties and cities.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>The scope of the operation is such that Beijing has allocated until now nearly $5 billion for the rescue relief fund.  Watch how Beijing&#39;s response to earthquake disaster is unprecedented. »</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Search-and-rescue help is also coming from outside the country. A team from Japan entered Sichuan province early Friday, Xinhua reported. Rescuers from Russia, South Korea and Singapore were expected to arrive soon.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Saudi Arabia, the United Kingdom, Germany, Vietnam and Poland were among the countries providing humanitarian assistance, according to Xinhua.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Meanwhile Louis Michel, Development Aid Commissioner to the EU, has said it will give initial emergency aid of $3.1 million to cover supplies including food and blankets, The Associated Press has reported, to demonstrate solidarity with China.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Attention is now also switching to preventing the possible spread of disease, with 60 funeral workers being sent to Sichuan province to cremate thousands of bodies, according to Xinhua.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Housing Minister Jiang Weixin has warned that water is not now flowing in at least 20 counties and cities in Sichaun, AP reported, making the supply situation &quot;extremely serious.&quot;</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Leading the country&#39;s disaster response, Chinese Premier Wen Jiabao praised the country for its &quot;efficiency and order&quot; in the midst of the disaster.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>&quot;Saving lives is still our top priority, as long as hope of survival still exists,&quot; Wen said, according to Xinhua.  Watch how rescuers search devastated town for earthquake survivors. »</p>
<p> </p>
<p>He added that it was more powerful than Tangshan earthquake in northern Hebei Province, which killed an estimated 240,000 people, the agency reported.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Don&#39;t Miss</p>
<p>iReport:  Your photos, videos </p>
<p>iReport.com: Send us your pictures, stories </p>
<p>Impact Your World </p>
<p>See how you can make a difference  </p>
<p>Hope is now running out for many trapped under tons of debris. The scene was especially painful in Beichuan, where parents of middle-school students waited Thursday, hoping recovery teams would pull their children alive from the rubble of a middle school.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>They found little hope as search teams pulled out one lifeless body after another.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>&quot;There are teenagers wearing jeans and gym shoes and their bodies are twisted,&quot; CNN&#39;s John Vause said, reporting from just outside the school. &quot;The expression on one girl&#39;s face was just pain -- she was dead.&quot;</p>
<p> </p>
<p>A few roads to Wenchuan county -- the epicenter of the quake -- started to open Thursday, allowing military trucks to begin their haul to affected sites, while rescuers continued attempts to save those trapped beneath the rubble at schools, businesses and homes.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Late in the day, a quake-damaged road from Lixian county into Wenchuan opened after around-the-clock repairs were completed, according to Xinhua.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Rescuers have been struggling to reach the worst-hit quake areas, battling landslides, buckled roads, collapsed bridges and inclement weather.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>More than 4.3 million homes collapsed or sustained damage because of the quake, according to the Chinese Embassy in Washington. </p>

</storyBody>
<mosExternalMetadata>
<mosScope>PLAYLIST</mosScope>
<mosSchema>http://DEMOENPS50VPC/schema/enps.dtd</mosSchema>
<mosPayload>
<SourceMediaTime>0</SourceMediaTime>
<SourceModBy>RREGAN</SourceModBy>
<SourceModTime>20070518151101</SourceModTime>
<SourceTextTime>0</SourceTextTime>
<Approved>0</Approved>
<ModBy>ADMINISTRATOR</ModBy>
<ModTime>20080516145604</ModTime>
<Owner>ADMINISTRATOR</Owner>
<Creator>RREGAN</Creator>
<TextTime>279</TextTime>
<MediaTime>0</MediaTime>
<ENPSItemType>3</ENPSItemType>
</mosPayload>
</mosExternalMetadata>
</roStorySend>
</mos>
